Okay, so we just got GrokBot, which is
probably the easiest way that I found to
be able to spin up teams of different AI
agents that you can use from your phone,
on your computer, everything stays
synced, and they're always on. It kind
of feels like you've got Claude Code,
Codex, and Hermes agent all in your
pocket. It's super easy to set up, so
let's just jump right in. So, what
you're going to want to do is go to
Google, type in GrokBot, and then click
on this link, and download this for
Windows, for Apple, and for your iOS
device, so everything stays synced
together. Now, this is super cool. This
is what it's going to look like. You can
have a ton of different agents on the
side, and you can talk to each one
individually, and you can have them
actually talking to each other, which is
super cool. Each of the bots have their
own computer, which is really cool. You
can sign in to a session, and it will
keep that login. You can record yourself
doing something on the bot's computer,
and then it will be able to just
replicate it like a skill, and there's
so many other things. They get smarter
over time. It's super cool. Now, in
order to try this out, you are going to
have to be on the Cursor Ultra plan, so
get the Ultra plan, then you can
download GrokBot, and play around. Okay,
so when you open the app, this is kind
of what it looks like. It's going to
first walk you through like, "Hey, this
is GrokBot. Create your first bot." You
can, you know, give it a name, and a
color, and a shape, and all this. And
then, once you're actually in here, and
you've made a few, it's going to look
like almost like an iMessage channel, or
like a Telegram channel. You have
different bots that you can switch
between. On the right-hand side, you're
going to have settings. You can give
them a name, a title, a description, and
then you can also look at their
computers. So, right here, you can see
that Klaus, my agent right here, is
inside of my school community, logged in
as me, and it's going through, and it's
liking posts that I wanted it to like.
So, it's controlling this browser, and I
also can, too, though. If I wanted to
come in here, and I wanted to, for
example, go to YouTube, I could log in
as myself if I wanted to, and then it
would stay logged in. It's even making
me do this little CAPTCHA thing. Wow,
this thing is really not letting me in.
Okay, there we go. Now, I can finally
get through to YouTube. You can see we
can also open up right here a file
manager. We could open up the terminal,
and we have this teach a task button,
which is where I could record myself
doing something, and then GrokBot would
automatically turn that into a skill,
which which what I did right here with
this AIS skill that it created. And now
it has this one called like 7-day
challenge posts on school. It went ahead
and ran it. And I've also got this thing
set up with my GitHub repo, my Herc 2,
as you can see, because that's where
I've been building my AI operating
system. So, if you guys are building
your own second brains and AI operating
systems, you can bring that into Grok
Bot and all of your agents that you
build can automatically have that
context. So, you're not starting over.
But, if you don't have an operating
system, that's completely fine because
when you create a new agent, it
basically onboards you. It asks you some
questions and it says, "Hey, what do you
want me to do for you?" So, right here
you can see I've got Klaus. He is my
executive assistant. I've got this Dev,
who is an AI engineer. And what's cool
is if I want Klaus to help me like build
a product, Klaus will actually delegate
work to my Dev because it knows what
they do. So, basically when you have an
agent, you give it a name, a title, and
a description. And the description's
basically almost like the same way
agents use skills. They say, "Okay,
cool. I have to do this task. Let me
look at all the other agents and see if
there's any agent whose description
matches this task. And if so, I will
just shoot them a message and then they
will help me out with that instead." So,
each agent that you build can be very
specialized to do very specific things.
If I come here to click on new chat, I
can start a chat with one of the bots.
Or if I want to go ahead and create my
own new bot, now I have the ability to
set this thing up however I want. You
can see right here it says, "Hey, good
to meet you. What do you want me around
for? Research and writing, something
specific, day-to-day work, whatever you
want." So, let's just make this agent
like my morning briefer. So, I just want
you to help me every morning plan my day
and look at what I have to do. And you
can see it says, "Okay, cool. I'm
checking what's already connected so I
know where to pull tasks from." And the
only thing that I've connected so far,
if I go to the plugins, is GitHub. I
need to connect things like Gmail,
Google Calendar, Slack, Google Drive,
ClickUp. All of these other things that
I use I need to connect. And it's just
as simple as a little sign-in. But,
what's cool about that is if you connect
GitHub for one agent, like my Klaus or
my Dev, then all of your different
agents will be able to use that
connection. So, they share those
plugins. It asked me where my to-dos and
calendar live and I just went ahead and
said Google Calendar and and Gmail and
now it's going to have me actually
connect those plugins. It's asking me if
I want to connect these. It says you'll
get a quick sign-in and then it's a
one-time setup. So, I'll click yes,
connect both. And so, it just pops up
like this and all you have to do is
click authorize and then you just do
your sign-in as you would in lots of
other apps. Okay, so we just connected
Gmail and Calendar and now it's asking
when do we actually run these morning
routine things. So, it's weekday
mornings by default. I'll pull today's
calendar and anything important in
Gmail. I'll just go ahead and say 7:00
a.m. Now, what does this mean? This
means that your agents can actually
create routines. And because all of this
is happening on the cloud, this will run
even if my computer's off, even if my
phone's off. You can see right here
created routine called morning day plan,
which shows up right here in the agent
section. So, these are the instructions.
Build Nate's morning plan and send it in
the chat. Look up current MCP tools,
calendar, Gmail. Pull today's calendar
events. Pull actionable Gmail items.
Write a short description. Blah, blah,
blah. And obviously, we could tweak this
instruction if we wanted to. It asks if
we want a sample. Yeah, I'll say run one
right now. So, this is so cool because
it makes it so easy to build
automations, to have different agents.
And as you can see in here, this one's
still called new bot. If I click on it
right here, I can give it a name. So,
I'm just going to call this one coffee
because it's a morning skill. I will
just say my morning planner. And then
you want to give this agent a super
specific one-liner of what it actually
does so that if Klaus or if my dev or
other agents needed to use it, it would
know to use this one. This agent looks
in my Gmail and my calendar to help me
plan my day every single weekday. And
then if you also want to play with the
way it looks, you can change the shape
and the color in here. You could also
generate it by describing it or you
could upload some sort of image. And
here's the cool part. Remember how
earlier I showed you guys how Klaus has
its own computer and right now it's open
on school as you can see or YouTube, I
guess. Coffee has its own screen.
And so does Dev. So, every time you're
building things with different agents,
they have their own computers and they
can do their own things. It's very cool.
Okay, so here is my sample for tomorrow,
what I'm going to get in the morning.
It's showing my day, it's showing the
meetings I have. It says here are things
worth acting on from email. So I've got
this thing that I need to get back to.
I've got this call on Thursday that I
have to respond to. I have got this chat
invite, very cool. And then it's
suggesting things like use 7:00 to 9:00
plan day to clear this item that you
have, to skim this notes and prepare for
that call, awesome. Your afternoon is
pretty stacked, so pick one of these
things and shorten your lunch and gym or
move the gym block, cool. It even told
me to protect my evening because I have
a dinner reservation tomorrow night. So
that's super cool because think about
this, I didn't tell it anything. All I
said was help me plan my day. And once I
iterate on this and say, "Hey, by the
way, here are some things I liked about
this, here are some things I didn't
like." It's going to get better and
better and smarter over time. And think
about how quick that whole skill and
whole routine was for me to set up. All
right, so I'm going to jump back over to
Klaus real quick. Take a look at this.
I had it do the skill where it went
through my preschool community and liked
posts that were for my 7-day challenge.
And here's what it did after a one run.
It said, "Okay, here's the dry run, here
are the three posts that I liked. Shout
out to you three community members, you
guys are awesome." And then it said,
"Hey, here's something I noticed. It's
not very clear, I can't tell very
clearly if they're liked or not
already." And then it said, "Okay, cool.
I went ahead and I put open the post
before liking into the skill." So
without me even asking it to, after it
ran the skill, it basically gave itself
feedback on what worked and what didn't.
And then it fixed itself. So over time,
it's going to get smarter every time it
runs the skills and it builds more
context and more memory over time as you
talk to it more and as you do more
things. Now you guys saw how quickly and
easy it was for me to create this
routine over here with Coffee. And what
I did here is I ran this based on a
schedule. So I ran this, you know,
weekdays at 7:00 a.m. But what else you
can do is you can run things here on
actual triggers. So on a Slack message,
on a GitHub event,
on a Teams message. These are currently
the triggers right now, just the same
way in IFTTT you had all these
different, you know, Gmail triggers and
things like that. I'm assuming that
these are going to become much, much
more broad. Like there's going to be
hundreds and hundreds of triggers in
here, but right now we're starting off
with just these six. So, watch this. I'm
going to create a new agent real quick,
and I'm going to call this one sort of
like my media agent, and I'm going to
connect this agent to Slack, and so that
it can basically notify me when there's
things going on in the Slack channels
that have to do with sponsorships or new
videos or new opportunities, anything to
do with the media side that I deal with
in Slack with a few different teams.
You're going to be helping me manage
media, sponsorships, things like that,
all within Slack. And so, you notice how
I'm spinning up agents to do very, very
specific things. Even on their website
on GrokBot, it's basically showing you
that agents should be doing one specific
job. Sales outbound, talent scout, paid
media, expense manager. If you try to
make one mega agent do a ton of
different things, it's just going to get
confused and all there's there's going
to be all these routines, it won't be as
good. But if you have each agent do one
specific job very well, and because you
have good descriptions and because you
have the ability for agents to talk to
each other, the jobs are going to still
get done. It's just the same way in
Claude code or codex, you like to have
your main orchestrator and you like to
have them basically delegate work to a
bunch of different little sub agents.
So, here's the Slack card that popped
up. I'm going to go ahead and authorize
into Slack real quick. It's asking what
Slack channels it should treat as home
base. I'm going to ask it what channels
can you actually see and read? Because
if you're like me in Slack, you might be
in a ton of different workspaces and
channels and things like that. So, it's
just worth seeing what it actually
knows. Now, look at this. It basically
was only able to see some of the stuff
inside one workspace, but I have another
email with some other channels I'm in,
right? So, I said, "Hey, I want to
connect another one." And it just lets
you add another one. So, here we have a
default connection, but now I also have
one that I'm calling work, and I can
sign in with a different account here so
that I can use different channels. There
we go. Now, I have authenticated another
Slack account, and it should be able to
see everything that I'm doing in there
now, which is great. Now, my GrokBot can
see into all of these public channels as
well as these private channels and DMs,
which is just great. So, what I want you
to do is help me set up a routine that's
on a Slack trigger. So, inside of the
default Slack workspace, what I want you
to do is when you get a message from
the um YouTube testing Nate channel, I
want that to trigger you to basically
give me a notification on what happened.
So, let's see if it's able to understand
what I'm saying and create us a routine
inside of its settings that's based on a
trigger rather than a time-based
routine. Okay, cool. So, it created a
routine called YouTube testing Nate
alerts. Perfect. You can see right here
it says when to run on new messages in
the YouTube testing Nate channel. So, it
founded the right channel, it created
the right trigger, and it set up the
actual instruction. So, before this
works, it says one setup step so it
actually fires is in that channel, you
have to run /invite @cursor. So, let me
just copy this command. The channel
listeners only hear channels the Cursor
Slack app is in. So, let me just go
ahead and try that real quick. I'm
inviting @cursor. There we go, it was
just added, and now in here, let's say
"Hey, a new sponsorship deal has come in
for 1,000,000,000
billion dollars for um a YouTube video.
The company is called Chipotle." Okay,
so I shot that off. Let's see what's
going on inside of Grok bot. Okay, so
we're seeing that it's having the little
new bot is working animation. It says
new bot because I haven't named this
yet. I haven't touched anything besides
sending that message in Slack. Boom. New
in YouTube testing Nate, you posted that
a Chipotle YouTube sponsorship deal came
in for this much money. Cool. So, that's
how you can see that that routine is
working, and that got set up so quickly.
With N and N, that might have taken me
maybe 15 minutes. With Claude code, that
may have taken me like
7 minutes. With this, this took like 2
minutes and one prompt. It's pretty
insane. And remember, you just want to
give your bots a name. I'll call this
guy money. The title will be Slack
media, and the description is basically
this agent is in charge of managing my
Slack communication for media and
sponsorships, things like that. Now, if
you wanted to reference some of the
skills or routines that this agent uses
and giving it more context for other
agents, that's perfectly fine. And it
even acknowledged that I named it money
and it said money works, I'll answer to
that from here. Okay, so what about
skills? How do skills work in here?
Well, if you do , you can run
skills like slash commands. So, the only
one that we've currently built, I
believe, was that school one. So, if I
type school, it says like 7-day
challenge posts on school, and I could
go ahead and use that skill if I want
to. So, skills work across all the
agents that you have, same thing with
plugins, but the computer sessions are
different and the descriptions of your
agents are different. Okay, now watch
this. I'm going to go to Klaus and let's
pretend, you know, because this is kind
of like my executive assistant, this is
what I'm going to be assuming is like my
router to different agents. I'm just
going to be like,
"Hey, I kind of forgot what's going on
with one of our most recent YouTube
videos, which you might be able to find
in the Slack channels. Uh maybe you
should just check in with Money to see
if he has any information about, you
know, what's going on with our Anthropic
reel or just what's been going on with
that." So, what this should do is it
should basically tell Klaus that, you
know, "I'm just an executive assistant,
but I can see that Money is a Slack
media agent. So, I'm going to go ahead
and shoot a message off to Money to take
care of that and then come back to me
and I'll answer to Nate in this main
session. There we go. It said pinging
Money about the Anthropic reel. It said
message Money, and if I click into this,
we can actually see the conversation.
It's view-only, but we can see what
Klaus said to Money, and we're going to
be able to see Money responding to Klaus
right here. Can you share the latest
status from Slack or whatever you have,
any blockers, next steps, blah blah
blah, keep it tight, I'll relay it to
him. So, there you go, you can see Money
just responded to Klaus, and then if I
go back to the main Klaus,
and if I go back to my conversation with
Klaus, it just responded right here. And
what else is cool is if I go to my
conversation with Money, it says, "Hey,
by the way, Klaus asked me about this."
So, they're not going to be able to keep
things secret, they're going to snitch
on each other if they're, you know,
being weird, but that's how that works
and I think that that is a super cool
feature. And I think that that really
encourages you to make sure that each
agent is very specialized because
they're able to easily talk to each
other. So, at this point, I've built out
these four agents. And what if I wanted
to turn off my computer and go for a
walk? Or maybe I'm even going on a
vacation. Well, guess what? On my phone,
I've got this exact same stuff. So, if I
open up Klaus on my phone, I have the
exact same messages and I can just say,
"Hey there." And what's going to happen
is that's going to come through. There,
I just sent it off. It comes through in
real time. So, everything is completely
synced because this is all in the cloud.
You don't even have to worry about
spinning up your own VPS or doing
anything locally. It all is just syncing
perfectly. The connectors still work. Um
all of their desktops still work. So, if
I go in here and I go to the browser,
remember how Klaus was over here on
YouTube? I can come into here on my
phone and I can also see what's going on
in here. And I can control this with my
phone. So, in right here on my phone,
I'm typing in um Nate Herc. I'm going to
go ahead and search for Nate Herc videos
on YouTube and I'm able to do this on my
phone. So, I'm controlling a cloud
computer from my phone, which is kind of
being managed over here by Klaus. It's
just very, very cool that this is being
set up so quickly for you.
Okay, so let's talk about what else
we've got in here and what are some
actual limitations. So, the first thing
is
how much am I going to use this? Will I
actually use this? Well, if I'm sitting
down at my desk and I am working on
knowledge work, if I'm trying to build
things, I will not be using this. I will
be using my Codex, my cloud code. That's
what I like to drive with when I'm
sitting down at my desk. Now, if I'm
traveling, if I'm in the back of an
Uber, if I'm on a vacation, if I'm
sitting at a restaurant, this is what
I'll be using because my phone syncs to
it right away and it just keeps things
super clean and super easy. That's kind
of the way that I distinguish between
Hermes agent right now and cloud code or
Codex is I just like to use my Hermes
when I'm on the go. And I think that
using this on the go is honestly much
better and much easier. Now, obviously,
this on the back end is using
a Grok model, right? It's not using my
Codex subscription or, you know,
Anthropic's APIs. It's not using those
models. So, if you really, really like
the other models way more, and if you
notice that you don't like the way that
the Grok models interact, then maybe you
won't use it as much. But, the way that
I'm thinking about this is I'm not going
to be building crazy software, crazy
apps from here. I'm more so going to be
doing things like checking in on things,
communicating to the team, reviewing
things, setting reminders, things like
that. Just very general knowledge work.
And obviously, I'm going to save my deep
dive, like my deep I need to be in flow
state for this kind of stuff. I'm going
to be saving that for when I'm sitting
down at my desk. Okay, so let's see what
else we have when we think about like
other settings and things. But, real
quick, I'm just going to send off this
message to Klaus. I'm asking him to
basically spin up a waiting list page,
and I told him to work with our AI
engineer. So, it's looping in dev.
They're going to get to work. Hopefully,
we're able to see something on a local
host on their cloud computer in a bit.
While they're working on that, let's go
over here to our settings. So, I'm going
to click on my name. I can see that I
have weekly usage. So, I've used 2%.
This resets in 7 days, and we can also,
you know, spend money. We talked about
getting this on iOS, and if I go to the
settings, let's see what else we have.
Your theme, your time zone, execution on
local computer. You can change the
permissions to be ask every time or
never allow. You can set rules so when
GrokBot wants to do certain things, you
should have it ask first or
automatically allow. Wow, that prototype
took like no time at all. Let's see if
we can open this up. So, if I click on
local host, we have it right here. Get
certified in AI automation without the
overwhelm. So, this is interesting
because it has good data, but it didn't
correctly use like our brand guidelines
and our logo. So, I wonder what the
issue is there. I wonder if it's because
it couldn't find it. I noticed that you
didn't really use our brand guidelines
as far as color scheme and logo. So,
just wanted to know why you didn't do
that. You know what's interesting about
this? It created this waitlist page in
our local host, because this is on my
Google Chrome. Whereas, if I wanted it
to do it on its own local host, that's
different. If it wanted it to do it on
its computer, it would have to build
that in a different way. So, as you guys
know how local host works, that's only
going to work on one local device, and
that's kind of cool that it created it
here locally for me on my actual
desktop, rather than doing it on their
cloud computer. It could do that, but we
just would have had to specify. And then
Klaus said, "Yeah, that's on me. When I
briefed Dev, I said to pick a sensible
default if branding wasn't handy, and
they assumed that AIS-ish was navy and
indigo. I didn't point them at brand
assets or Herc 2 packaging. Do you want
me to do that again?" I'm just going to
say yes, and we'll take a look at that
version. But anyways, that's basically
it. It's really just a matter of getting
in here, connecting in some of your
business context, and then just building
out a bunch of essentially different
skills, I would say. Different skills,
different sub-agents, and then just
seeing how you can have them work
together, and just spin up your routines
as quick as you can, because they're
super quick and easy to set up. If you
want to take a look at all the other
plugins, you just click on plugin, you
can scroll through, and you can search
for them. If you want to connect certain
custom ones, you certainly can, and you
can also see all of your actual skills
in here. These are skills that I have
made. I've only made one so far. This is
where we can update the name, the
description, the instructions, and you
can also go ahead and delete them. Now,
look how cool this is. Klaus found the
brand guidelines, and then it messaged
Dev, and here is the new message and the
chain between Klaus and Dev. They talked
about the prototype, Dev delivered it,
and then Klaus came back and said, "Hey,
here's the actual brand guidelines.
Here's the logo and the brand guideline
doc." And now Dev is saying, "Hey, I got
this from Klaus. I have to restyle the
waitlist, blah blah blah." So, I think
you guys get the point. They're talking
to each other. We have routine set up.
We can keep building these things really
easily, and
I think that this is just super cool
that I'm able to continue my work on my
phone super easily. Now, one thing that
I think, when you sort of look at tools
like this, is you don't want to get
carried away or caught up in the hype of
these tools, because yes, they're cool
and they're fun to play around with, but
don't just start forcing all these
agents and routines that you don't
actually need. Really think about what
is constraining your business, what are
the pain points that you're feeling on
the day-to-day, and does this tool solve
some of those pain points? For me, I'm
going to try to set up all of the Hermes
agents that I have right in here and I
think it's going to feel more cohesive
because they can talk to each other more
easily than the way I have them setting
up talking to each other in Hermes. But
if you actually don't have a need, if
you don't have a problem to solve with
this tool, then it might just be a waste
of time if you spent like all week
playing with it. You know, I think it's
cool and it's fun, but if you really
want to talk about like if you need it,
it's good to sort of think about that
element, right? So, this should be done.
I'm going to go into the wait list and
I'm going to hard refresh. Boom. Okay,
this looks way more on brand. There's
still some design things that I don't
love about it, but all I said was, "Hey,
build me a super simple wait list form."
I don't even know if this actually leads
anywhere. We would have to like keep
iterating if we wanted the dev to
actually make this go to ClickUp or
something like that. We definitely
could, but on a first pass, you can see
that it was able to look inside of my
repo. I had had it had all the context
of what's going on with this program and
it built it out for me super quick. But
anyways, that is going to do it for
today. I hope that this showed you
what's possible with this tool. As they
release new updates, I'm going to be
excited to cover them. Hopefully, we get
some cool stuff. Hopefully, we get the
automations and the routines to become
easier and easier to build with
different triggers. I'm super excited to
see how this tool evolves. So, if you
enjoyed or you learned something new,
please give it a like. It helps me out a
ton and as always, I appreciate you guys
making it to the end of the video and
I'll see you on the next one.
Thanks, everyone.